niim.co.in 2017-05-27

# Niim | Privacy policy

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CAREFULLY**  
THIS PRIVACY POLICY DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY POLICY OF NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF INTERNET MARKETING (NIIM) WEBSITE LOCATED AT http://niim.co.in/ AND ITS RELATED APPS (MOBILE OR OTHER). IF YOU ARE UNDER 18, PLEASE BE SURE TO READ THE PRIVACY POLICY UNDER THE GUIDANCE OF YOUR PARENTS AND SEEK THEIR HELP WHEREVER NECESSARY.

**This privacy policy applies to NIIM (www.niim.co.in)**  
We value your privacy and appreciate your trust in us. As a result, we would like to inform you regarding the way we would use your personal data. We recommend you to read this privacy policy so that you understand our approach towards the use of your personal data.

This Policy describes how we treat user information we collect on www.niim.co.in and other offline sources. This Privacy Policy applies to current and former visitors to our website. By visiting and/or using our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

www.niim.co.in (business and domain owned by National Institute of Internet Marketing (NIIM)”, an Indian Company registered under the Companies Act, 2011 having its registered office address B1/1, Near Janakpuri East Metro station, opposite pillar number no. 542, New Delhi - 110058) recognizes the importance of maintaining your privacy.

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
**a. Contact information :** We might collect your email, name, contact numbers like mobile number, phone number, street, city, state, postal code, country and IP address.  
**b. Information you post :** We collect information you post in a public space on our website or on a third-party social media site belonging to www.niim.co.in  
**c. Other information :** If you use our website, we may collect information about your IP address and the browser you're using. We might look at what site you came from, duration of time spent on our website, pages accessed or what site you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of mobile device you are using, or the version of the operating system your computer or device is running.

**2\. WE COLLECT INFORMATION IN DIFFERENT WAYS**  
**a. We collect information from you passively :** We use tracking tools like Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, browser cookies and web beacons for collecting information about your usage of our website.  
**b. We collect information directly from you :** We collect information directly from you when you fill any listed web form on our website. We also collect information if you post a comment on our websites or ask us a question through phone or email.  
**c. We get information about you from third parties :** For example, if you use an integrated social media feature on our websites. The third-party social media site will give us certain information about you. This could include your name and email address.

**3\. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
**a. We use information to contact you :** We might use the information you provide to contact you for confirmation of a purchase on our website or for other promotional purposes.  
**b. We use information to respond to your requests or questions :** We might use your information to confirm your query for the course offered by our company.  
**c. We use information to improve our products and services :** We might use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences.  
**d. We use information to look at site trends and customer interests :** We may use your information to make our website and courses better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.  
**e. We use information for security purposes :** We may use information to protect our company, our aspirants, or our websites.  
**f. We use information for marketing purposes :** We might send you information about special promotions or offers. We might also tell you about new features or course. These might be our own offers or courses, or third-party offers or courses we think you might find interesting. Or, for example, if you fill any listed web form in our website, we'll enroll you in our newsletter.  
**g. We use information to send you transactional communications :** We might send you emails or SMS as reply to your query. We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

**4\. SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD-PARTIES**  
**a. We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf :** We share information with mentors or trainers or registered vendor who help us to manage our online form filling and online enrollment process or transactional message processors. Some vendors may be located outside of India.  
**b. We will share information with the seminar or workshop or any event organizers :** We share your information with the seminar or the workshop or any event organizers and other parties responsible for fulfilling the enrollment obligation. The event organizers and other parties may use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.  
**c. We will share information with our business partners :** This includes a third party who provide or sponsor our seminar, workshop or event, or who operates a venue where we hold seminar, workshop or events. Our partners use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.  
**d. We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves :** We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud.  
**e. We may share your information for reasons not described in this policy :** We will tell you before we do this.

**5\. Email Opt-Out**  
**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails:**  
**To stop receiving our promotional emails, please email unsubscriber@niim.co.in. It may take about ten days to process your request. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still be sending you transactional messages through email and SMS about your enrollment.**

**6\. Third party sites**  
**If you click on one of the links to third party websites, you may be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites.**

**7\. Grievance Officer**  
**In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:**  
**GRievence officer detailsof NIIM**
